#### Contact

Purwokerto, Banyumas, Jawa Tengah 081934167842 (Mobile) fibewoyo@gmail.com

www.linkedin.com/in/amalnurfaizi (LinkedIn)

### Top Skills

React.js

UIUX

**Technical Support** 

### Certifications

Merancang desain aplikasi mobile UIUX

Belajar Membuat Aplikasi Kognitif Manajemen dan Tata Kelola TI

Honors-Awards
FINALIST UI/UX DESIGN
COMPETITION

# **Amal Nur Faizi**

software engineer

Wangon, Central Java, Indonesia

## Summary

A passionate new graduate in the field of full-stack development. I also possess a strong understanding of UI/UX design to create engaging and user-friendly interfaces. Through my internship experience, I have honed my skills in designing, building, and testing efficient and reliable software solutions while ensuring quality through systematic QA/QC processes.

# Experience

Badan Amil Zakat Nasional (BAZNAS) IT Specialist October 2023 - Present (1 year 3 months) Banyumas, Central Java, Indonesia

SMK Bunda Satria Wangon Information Technology Support Officer January 2022 - November 2023 (1 year 11 months)

Wangon, Jawa Tengah, Indonesia

Badan Pengelola Keuangan Dan Aset Daerah Provinsi Jawa Tengah Government Kabupaten Banyumas

July 2023 - September 2023 (3 months)

Purwokerto, Central Java, Indonesia

Alterra Indonesia UI Designer November 2022 - January 2023 (3 months) Indonesia

## Education

Institut Teknologi Telkom

Bachelor of Technology - BTech, Teknik Software Komputer · (January 2019 - June 2023)

SMA Negeri 1 Dayeuhluhur Ilmu Pengetahuan Sosial · (July 2016 - July 2019)